Heroes are made in America.
G.I. Joe: Retaliation is a action, science fiction,
adventure film directed by Jon M. Chu.
Framed for crimes against the country, the G.I.
Joe team is terminated by Presidential order.
This forces the G.I.
Joes into not only fighting their mortal enemy Cobra; they are forced to contend with
threats from within the government that jeopardize their very existence.
Marvin Hinton / Roadblock, played by Dwayne Johnson.
Joe Colton, played by Bruce Willis.
U.S. President, played by Jonathan Pryce.
Jaye Burnett / Lady Jaye, played by Adrianne Palicki.
Snake Eyes, played by Ray Park.
Firefly, played by Ray Stevenson.
Joe: Retaliation is a 2013 American military science
fiction action film based on the G.I.
Joe toy line.
It is the second installment in the G.I.
Joe film series and the stand-alone sequel to G.I.
Joe: The Rise of Cobra (2009).
Directed by Jon M.
Chu and written by Rhett Reese and Paul Wernick, the
film features an ensemble cast starring D.
Cotrona, Lee Byung-hun, Adrianne Palicki, Ray Park, Jonathan Pryce, Ray
Stevenson, Channing Tatum, Bruce Willis, and Dwayne Johnson.
Joes fight their enemy Cobra again and also face
threats from within the US government.
Originally slated for release in June 2012, the film was delayed to
convert to 3D and boost interest in international markets.
Joe: Retaliation was released in the United States on
March 28, 2013, by Paramount Pictures.
The film, like its predecessor, received generally negative reviews from critics, although it was considered an
improvement from its predecessor and grossed $375.7 million worldwide against a budget of $130–155 million.
The film explores themes of rescue, assassin, technology, missile, warhead.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.